<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="page_scraping" model="website.page">
            <field name="name">Scraping</field>
            <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="key">prixite_website.scraping</field>
            <field name="url">/services/scraping</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="Scraping" t-name="prixite_website.scraping">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                      <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/prixite_theme/static/scss/service.scss" />
                        <xpath expr="//title" position="replace">
                <t t-set="title">Prixite - Scraping</t>
            </xpath>
                        <div class="container mt-5 text-black mt-3 mt-md-5 p-md-0">
                            <div class="row align-items-center p-4 services-containerr"
                                 style="background-color: #EFF7EC; border-radius: 1rem;">
                                <div class="col-md-8">
                                    <h3>Scraping</h3>
                                    <p class="service-para">Prixite is one of the leading digital marketing service providers that believe in
                                        creating value added solutions for our potential clients web data extraction
                                        needs.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                               <div class="col-12 col-md-4 text-center text-end">
                                    <a href="/contact-us" class="btn  btn-mobile-small btn-contact submit-button"
                                    >
                                        CONTACT US
                                        <svg width="16px" height="16px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"
                                             xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_bgCarrier" stroke-width="0"></g>
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_tracerCarrier" stroke-linecap="round"
                                               stroke-linejoin="round"></g>
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_iconCarrier">
                                                <path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd"
                                                      d="M1.265 4.42619C1.04293 2.87167 2.6169 1.67931 4.05323 2.31397L21.8341 10.1706C23.423 10.8727 23.423 13.1273 21.8341 13.8294L4.05323 21.686C2.6169 22.3207 1.04293 21.1283 1.265 19.5738L1.99102 14.4917C2.06002 14.0087 2.41458 13.6156 2.88791 13.4972L8.87688 12L2.88791 10.5028C2.41458 10.3844 2.06002 9.99129 1.99102 9.50829L1.265 4.42619ZM21.0257 12L3.2449 4.14335L3.89484 8.69294L12.8545 10.9328C13.9654 11.2106 13.9654 12.7894 12.8545 13.0672L3.89484 15.3071L3.2449 19.8566L21.0257 12Z"
                                                      fill="#ffffff"></path>
                                            </g>
                                        </svg>
                                    </a>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <div class=" align-items-center mt-4 mt-md-5"
                            >
                                <div>
                                    <p  class="sub-para-service">Prixite is one of the top digital marketing service providers to its extensive
                                        clientele all around the world. The key to our success is providing customized
                                        solutions that fit your business needs by thoroughly understanding your target
                                        market and offering you a customized plan to achieve your goals. One of the most
                                        inventive and cost-effective solutions the business needs of our client when it
                                        comes to web data extraction is data scarping. Our entire objective is to make
                                        data scraping simple and accessible for our clients. We offer various services
                                        when it comes to data scrapping that can truly innovate and bring value to their
                                        business dynamics. These services include:
                                    </p>
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Configuring and utilizing the data scrapper services by just clicking and pointing at the elements. There is no requirement for coding at all.</li>
                                        <li>Our data scraping software allows you to extract data from various websites having multiple-level navigation such as categories and subcategories, product pages, pagination, and much more.</li>
                                        <li>Our data scraping tool is designed in a way to deal with modern interfaced websites that use JavaScript frameworks and also allows clients to experience page scroll down, pagination handlers, Ajax requests, and much more.</li>
                                        <li>Our inventive data scrapping software also allows you to develop site maps from various types of selectors to experience tailored data extraction from different sites having different structures.</li>
                                        <li>Another amazing feature of our data scraping software is that it allows users to export the extracted data in CSV, XLSV, and JSON formats directly from the browser which you can easily access via API and webhooks. Or you may also use Dropbox to export the extracted data.</li>
                                    </ul>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
