<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="page_web_development" model="website.page">
            <field name="name">Web Development</field>
            <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
            <field name="key">prixite_website.web_development</field>
            <field name="url">/services/web-development</field>
            <field name="type">qweb</field>
            <field name="arch" type="xml">
                <t name="Web Development" t-name="prixite_website.web_development">
                    <t t-call="website.layout">
                     <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/prixite_theme/static/scss/service.scss" />
                        <xpath expr="//title" position="replace">
                <t t-set="title">Prixite - Web Development</t>
            </xpath>
                        <div class="container mt-3 mt-md-5 text-black p-md-0">
                            <div class="row align-items-center p-4 services-containerr"
                                 style="background-color: #EFF7EC; border-radius: 1rem;">
                                <div class="col-md-8">
                                    <h3>Web App Development</h3>
                                    <p class="service-para">Prixite being the exquisite web development brands offers innovative solutions to
                                        your web development needs in today’s dynamics.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-12 col-md-4 text-center text-end">
                                    <a href="/contact-us" class="btn  btn-mobile-small btn-contact submit-button"
                                     >
                                        CONTACT US
                                        <svg width="16px" height="16px" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"
                                             xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_bgCarrier" stroke-width="0"></g>
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_tracerCarrier" stroke-linecap="round"
                                               stroke-linejoin="round"></g>
                                            <g id="SVGRepo_iconCarrier">
                                                <path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd"
                                                      d="M1.265 4.42619C1.04293 2.87167 2.6169 1.67931 4.05323 2.31397L21.8341 10.1706C23.423 10.8727 23.423 13.1273 21.8341 13.8294L4.05323 21.686C2.6169 22.3207 1.04293 21.1283 1.265 19.5738L1.99102 14.4917C2.06002 14.0087 2.41458 13.6156 2.88791 13.4972L8.87688 12L2.88791 10.5028C2.41458 10.3844 2.06002 9.99129 1.99102 9.50829L1.265 4.42619ZM21.0257 12L3.2449 4.14335L3.89484 8.69294L12.8545 10.9328C13.9654 11.2106 13.9654 12.7894 12.8545 13.0672L3.89484 15.3071L3.2449 19.8566L21.0257 12Z"
                                                      fill="#ffffff"></path>
                                            </g>
                                        </svg>
                                    </a>
                                </div>
                            </div>

                            <div class="align-items-center mt-4 mt-md-5"
                                 >
                                <div>
                                    <p  class="sub-para-service">To be a distinctive and top-notch brand in the competitive business world, every
                                        business requires a sound website that can leave an impact on the customer’s
                                        mind. A sound website is the need of the hour for the rapid progress and
                                        sustainability of the business. Prixite aims to utilize its expertise in
                                        understanding our potential customer’s vision and turning it into a believable
                                        output in the form of a compelling website that generates revenues and traffic
                                        for each of our worthy clients.
                                    </p>
                                    <br></br>
                                    <p  class="sub-para-service">Prixite truly understands the importance of a well-constructed website that may
                                        exceed your expectations when it comes to usability and performance. Having a
                                        team of experienced and professional full-stack web developers and designers, we
                                        offer our clients a variety of web development services such as UX expertise,
                                        inventive UI designs, updated programming language, incomparable DevOps, and the
                                        best full-stack developers to ensure the provision of cost-effective solutions
                                        to our clients. Our website development process is thoroughly systematic and
                                        streamlines according to the need and expectations of our clients.
                                    </p>
                                    <br></br>
                                    <p  class="sub-para-service">It starts with understanding the requirements and queries related to the business
                                        of our clients based on which we create the suitable timeline and plan of the
                                        project. Then comes the entire focus on creating a unique user experience and
                                        sophisticated web interface that truly resonates with the brand image of the
                                        clients. The third step involves developing and designing a custom-coded website
                                        with an innovative interface that conveniently covers your business need into a
                                        reliable brand image. And final steps involve the quality check, deploying, and
                                        maintenance of your website.
                                    </p>
                                       <br></br>
                                    <p  class="sub-para-service">We offer our clients progressive web development solutions that truly contribute
                                        to expanding their business by removing marketing obstacles and focusing on the
                                        leading key performance indicators of our client’s business that sets them apart
                                        from their competitors.
                                    </p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>